{
  "relationships": {
    "many_classes": [
      "answers"
    ],
    "single_classes": [
      "students",
      "questions"
    ]
  },
  "classes": [
    "students",
    "questions",
    "answers"
  ],
  "data": {
    "students": [
      {
        "_id": "123",
        "firstName": "Alice",
        "lastName": "Wonderland",
        "username": "alice",
        "password": "alice",
        "gradYear": 2020,
        "scholarship": 15000
      },
      {
        "_id": "234",
        "firstName": "Bob",
        "lastName": "Hope",
        "username": "bob",
        "password": "bob",
        "gradYear": 2021,
        "scholarship": 12000
      }
    ],
    "answers": [
      {
        "_id": "123",
        "student": "123",
        "question": "321",
        "trueFalseAnswer": true
      },
      {
        "_id": "234",
        "student": "123",
        "question": "432",
        "trueFalseAnswer": false
      },
      {
        "_id": "345",
        "student": "123",
        "question": "543",
        "multipleChoiceAnswer": 1
      },
      {
        "_id": "456",
        "student": "123",
        "question": "654",
        "multipleChoiceAnswer": 2
      },
      {
        "_id": "567",
        "student": "234",
        "question": "321",
        "trueFalseAnswer": false
      },
      {
        "_id": "678",
        "student": "234",
        "question": "432",
        "trueFalseAnswer": true
      },
      {
        "_id": "789",
        "student": "234",
        "question": "543",
        "multipleChoiceAnswer": 3
      },
      {
        "_id": "890",
        "student": "234",
        "question": "654",
        "multipleChoiceAnswer": 4
      }
    ],
    "questions": [
      {
        "_id": "321",
        "question": "Is the following schema valid?",
        "points": 10,
        "type": "TRUE_FALSE",
        "isTrue": false
      },
      {
        "_id": "432",
        "question": "DAO stands for Dynamic Access Object.",
        "points": 10,
        "type": "TRUE_FALSE",
        "isTrue": false
      },
      {
        "_id": "543",
        "question": "What does JPA stand for?",
        "points": 10,
        "type": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
        "choices": [
          "Java Persistence API",
          "Java Persisted Application",
          "JavaScript Persistence API",
          "JSON Persistent Associations"
        ],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "_id": "654",
        "question": "What does ORM stand for?",
        "points": 10,
        "type": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE",
        "choices": [
          "Object Relational Model",
          "Object Relative Markup",
          "Object Reflexive Model",
          "Object Relational Mapping"
        ],
        "correct": 3
      }
    ]
  },
  "schema": {
    "students": [
      "_id",
      "firstName",
      "lastName",
      "username",
      "password",
      "gradYear",
      "scholarship"
    ],
    "answers": [
      "_id",
      "student",
      "question",
      "trueFalseAnswer",
      "multipleChoiceAnswer"
    ],
    "questions": [
      "_id",
      "question",
      "points",
      "type",
      "choices",
      "correct"
    ]
  }
}